http://www.ringware.com/privacy-policy/

Categories
Class Jewelry »
Barnard College
Dartmouth College
Harvard University
Hobart & William Smith Colleges »
Yale University
Team Awards »
Rings »
Band
Heritage
Signet
Tank
Jewelry »
Search
Loading... Please wait...
Categories
Class Jewelry »
Barnard College
Dartmouth College
Harvard University
Hobart & William Smith Colleges »
Yale University
Team Awards »
Rings »
Band
Heritage
Signet
Tank
Jewelry »
Privacy Policy
Signitas is committed to safeguarding your privacy.  Below, you will find information about Signitas' commitment to securing the privacy of your personally identifiable information.  By visiting Signitas.com you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
Secure Online Ordering
We strive to maintain the privacy and security of your transactions with us by protecting your personal and credit card information.  Signitas.com uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) authentication to protect the confidentiality and privacy of online transactions through our site.  SSL authentication and 128-bit encryption (scrambling) ensures that your online transaction and credit card information are safe from third party interception.  Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers.
Information We Collect
We only collect personally identifiable information on our website that you choose to share with us when subscribing to our newsletter, using our contact form, registering for an account or placing an order.  The information you provide to us, such as your name, email address, mailing address and phone number, will be stored by our systems.  Your order, communications sent through our website and meta-data associated with the communication may be stored to enable us to better assist you in the future.  The information we collect is transmitted using SSL technology, the approved industry standard.
How We Use Collected Information
Personal information submitted to us though our website may be used to:
send you email notifications associated with your purchase;
send you goods purchased through our website;
send you an email notification or newsletter that you have specifically requested (you may opt out of receiving the newsletter at any time);
send you marketing communications related to our business that we think may be of interest to you, etc.
We do not share, sell, rent or barter any personally identifiable information to any third party without your permission.  Our site may contain links to other sites.  Signitas is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.
Cookies
Like many websites, Signitas.com uses cookies to provide a better browsing experience.  A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser.  Cookies are stored by the browser to ensure ease of login, checkout, etc.  Personally identifiable information cannot be obtained, stored or shared via cookies.  In addition, Signitas.com uses analytics cookies to analyze the use of our website so that we can continuously improve our users' experience.  By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance this policy.  Most browsers give you the options to refuse and delete stored cookies.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at (800) 643-3776 or info@signitas.com.
Copyright © 2020 Signitas, Inc., Inc. All Rights Reserved.
We accept Visa, MasterCard, Discover, Paypal, AmericanExpress
